[Music]
Oh
hello everyone welcome to the natatorium
at the Nanjing Olympic sport center
we've arrived at the final individual
event the men's 10 metre platform
perhaps the most prestigious event - the
more don't forget though this is not the
traditional finale to the diving
competition we've still got the
International with team event to come
which is a real innovation here at the
Youth Olympic Games but now that we're
up on that really tall platform and that
means we're staging a fascinating
rematch in one of the big rivalries that
provided some excellent competition here
in the pool the host nations young how
is looking to emulate the great human
bone who were double gold at these games
four years ago in Singapore and has gone
on to World Championship Olympic success
all the way in the three meter event
before the Chinese tiger grabbed the
gold they beat each other over ten
meters another excellent competition on
the cars here champagne has already won
both women's individual titles here in
Nanjing camp yeah how making another
double-double for the world's greatest
diving nation
crowd here already in this auditorium
let's just sort out the format in this
so preliminary competition nine rounds
of diving ahead of these eleven divers
it's a testing session the first four
rounds comprised of dives with a total
degree of difficulty limited to seven
point six fact in reality there'll be a
lot less than that the marks of these
are carried forward into the final so
this plenary really does count towards
the medals after that the divers move on
to the more ambitious dyes so a further
five range with no limit on the degree
of difficulty in many ways that's where
the show begins
judges our boy stirred away from each
other and from everybody else remember
seven judges top and bottom two are
struck off we're left with the little
three that can't they're added together
multiplied by the degree of difficulty
and that is what you shall get as we
said 11 competitors yeah I will be
second up and we'll get the biggest
cheer of course but keep an eye out for
number nine from Mexico Rodrigo Diego
Lopez he has a good rivalry with Chinese
diver Singaporeans will get some support
here we've already heard some cheers for
him as we introductions here in the
Torian for these divers remember some of
them very young indeed 15 16 years of
age this is the biggest stage they've
been on and the highest platform of
course after the 3-meter springboard we
can I believe daunted it certainly to
these early on will be very simple in
terms of difficulty twos that sort of
thing afterwards it will get quite
interesting yang for example is gone for
three point four and three point five
some of these divers just
a little sing-along these headphones
just to block out the PA the crowd the
other competitors get yourself into the
zone rehearse your dives in your head
get the tape on to protect the wrist as
you enter the water from such a height
I'm very close to getting under way here
in the men's 10 metre platform the
preliminary dives nine rounds dollies
they have to perfect and they'll be
breathing deeply at this point they've
been practicing for quite some time
we'll start with Bennett check him choke
1503 metre platform it's computed
repeating in both these disciplines from
Kiev the Ukrainian once we get out of
the way
thick and fast this was a moment and
wait for this first of all the
competition
understand forward somersault with my
the difficulty
I'm a simple dive executed well by the
Ukrainian there's of course a trade-off
between the amount of difficulty and how
easy you can from the dive of course a
pretty decent dollar kept it very
straight good in that white position as
well five point six now for the crows to
get behind this man here one point sixty
difficulty forward one-and-a-half
somersault
we're I'd like it nicely done
well the Chinese athlete good attack I
think the judges will like that one
ix almost across the board 43.2 for the
[Music]
and I'm gonna get some
go away the 18 year old sound forward
seven so 1.9 the difficulty
[Applause]
first art out of the way for the
European junior champion you love the
bronze in those championships in the 10
meter
in 2/3 so impress the judges they're in
our house take forward 40 2.75 Ukrainian
is on top of the pile now the German do
you know Bart out somersault difficulty
of - it's the most difficult we've seen
so far these early stages
[Applause]
executed it pretty well possibly
giving the entry completely right on the
knees that's what the judges like to see
a pretty good entry as well the judges
will give him eights in several houses
the degree of difficulty means that he
gets 47 points that goes top of the pile
at the moment the armenian sorry so this
is another two three difficulty dive the
inward and one hour half somersaults
they look good from here
nice
straight the judges weren't so impressed
marked him down a little bit sixes total
score of 36 we've seen now the Canadian
hip Gagne excellent bronze medal at the
three meter events this is a forward of
what a half somersault most difficult
dive just a degree of difficulty of 1.6
game that's what the judge like to see
the legs and the face brought together
seven and a half thirty four point four
into six place an Egyptian
it's up to dial is here so it's a
forward dive
Oh simple dive nicely executed through
difficulty just one and a half getting
his face that close to the legs that's
what the judges like the seat
what it scores six four thousand seven s
but of course a difficulty not so just
have a place with 30 points the
Colombian Kevin Garcia Alvarez so
forward one and a half cent of salt six
the degree of difficulty I said treat
these times early on the simpler dives
but remember the scores in forward to
the final round later on today so it is
important to get these right before you
start your show voting the judges and
then 6.5 scrubbed through thirty three
point six and taking it to seventh place
now then mr. Mexican the arrival to the
Chinese Rodrigo Diego and Lopez
four and a half seven salt game up to
difficulty one point six degree of
difficulty being the position she does
it won't fix humility there
thirty-six to score seven for house the
judge is all the way through modest for
the Mexican that there's lots of rounds
to go
now the Frenchman if it is Xander with a
forward one a half somersault in fact
Carlin copy of the next kids dive
that was a little bit sharper
[Applause]
I saw speed on the dive there
Kentucky nicely as well seven judges
6.45 17.5 they won't go that's it for
the frigid a spot like no means least we
have the Singaporean is it Jonathan Chan
you know the owner rotation there of the
forward of what are seven salt 160
degree of difficulty seventeen-year-old
only competing in the Terminator
this man in Singapore and he will 11 out
of 11 after the first ice
so this is how it stands after the first
round long way to go but she fell apart
out typically diving as well
he's top of the road kids a long way to
go all these athletes ready to go in
this second round
get underway the van here is second in
the standings at the moment the
seventeen-year-old from the Ukraine in
the 18 in November in would somersault
similar in difficulty to his first dive
just to the degree of difficulty
this will touch the bone rotation but he
got the pipe nicely
to the effort flexibility the diver
needs just a little bit perhaps
so decent marks the judges 46 even there
or there abouts in the mix as we go to a
split around the big favorite yarn how
you know ripple around this auditorium
would one of them have somersault as
well
same degree of difficulty as the
Ukranian
the entry was better the coach likes it
it's not quite as smart in the pike
position look at this entry
they
the judges have liked that one look at
that nine-point fines across the board
57 the score
[Music]
that's enough to put him into the lead
early on in his second round lot of
divers to come here's the next one
always Daniel Jensen forward 1/2
somersault
little bit over on the entry there as
tied to the Sun we've seen get in the
bike gotta get out of that nice and
early and then land it too bad at all
[Music]
fiddling marks six point five seven
thirty two point eight he's not
particularly happy with a few words of
wisdom for him and t-mobile tell you the
mix junior champion last month you
should die before wouldn't have
somersaults stronger at the springboard
if truth be told
fourth in that which is a horrible
horrible position to come
rotating tidied Ivo reflected in the
judges scores 33.6 the most difficult
dive so you've got to really now these
have saigo-san
forward one and a half seven salt one
point sixty degree of difficulty the
only being in this technical addition
not the three metre long time to wait
for his chance
point getting straight and eventually
into the water
right position not quite hitting the
entry properly and again reflected in
the judges scores seven 106.5 32.8 we
put him into fifth place as we're going
through this second round of nine now
the Canadian if you leave me eight
members of course in the three meter
entry that's not what he would have
wanted but the dive itself was pretty
good inward one-and-a-half somersault to
do if definitely is to so that one
helping a little bit a little bit look
at that
really tight Mike
untidy on that entry into the water the
degree of difficulty helps him he gets
forty four point seven the judges
Egypt's our court he is coached by the
way is a professor in micro coil as
you're not sure how that helps certainly
join themselves here at the Youth
Olympic Games simple dives just a one
point eight degree of difficulty fairly
sharp crisp dive the 17-year old shack
the good entry
76.5 it's respectable for the Egyptian
now the Colombian Kevin see ya
Alvarez need to give to 30 of to would
one and a half somersault here youngest
no divert 15 a little bit of over
rotation that he entered the water it's
not as sharp as you would like executing
the dive
it's not overly excited their score a 40
though he was decent 6007 the contenders
Rodrigo Diego Lopez is the even word
women are sort of softness and his
forward with a mask some summits in the
first round but take him tight on the
pike but difficulty will help him with
the marks from the judges as Christmas I
think he would've liked nice quickly
entry the judges overleaf he will go
into fourth place ready
Chinese athlete
none of these first four dives once
carried forward to the final as well
he's said France with the inward
one-and-a-half somersault just seen
pretty good to me
[Applause]
the pike it nicely
the if she was pretty good as well
finished
12 12 in the 3-meter one dive went badly
arrived that really high boy shot him
that's a very solid dive 45 points for
the Frenchman and then from Singapore
with an inward one-and-a-half somersault
we've seen a few of these in this round
to gain a degree of difficulty
irrelevant so that were my eyes but II
didn't like as crisp as he would have
liked
I think the entry will be marked down by
the judges as well situation not that
close
he's had two replies from the judges
seven laughs he'll get 45 I'll drag him
up into ninth place so that's the second
round of nine and it's going very well
for the home fans you've turned up in
fair numbers see yang how look for
another gold medal here delivery frames
of course Egypt's core deep bringing up
the rear a long way to go here remember
four dives the first four dives there's
a cap up the degree of difficulty these
are the points that will be put forward
into the final later on today
so 7 primes still to go in this big
Murray long way to go important my
degree of differently dyes to come later
on so things can change quite quickly
village ting Kok North Ukraine gets us
underway in round three with a back dive
nicely done
simple but if you nail it it can't be as
effective
so stumbling over a difficult dive she
is holding the position and then looking
for the entry points
look at that ates 18.5 struck off so
that's good for the Ukrainian it'd be
happy with that now here's the valley of
the top of the pile after the end of the
second round yeah how that already has a
gold at three meters with a reverse dive
crowd liked it of course a lot of people
have arrived early here auditorium to
see this man disappointed so far
four five six
look at that and ten from one of the
judges you've had three tents from the
judges 9.5 and nines and that is a
really really good score
goodness me really is in the form of
fifty five ten high score as well in the
second round but I'll have to put that
out of his mind and just get on with his
dive reverse we're gonna have sort of
salt and a half twist
I was down there yeah I said
it's not the most straightforward dyes
that you would win a half somersault
headed myself there
about entry the Norwegian an
eighteen-year-old
citizens
for a 42 put it into third place now we
have t-mobile tell as I mentioned a
difficult one that's been two point one
the degree of difficulty the reversible
don't have cell so half twist
and then she wasn't great maybe not
dying for that
was a difficult die though so I will go
in his favor
remember the middle three scores are
taken and it's multiplied by the degree
of difficulty that's how we get our
scores here yeah just a little bit of
over rotation
six of house on the schools that will
count forty-nine five is the score will
be registered in this third round that
in Romania there saki-san he did in the
world championships in 24th in the
10-meter events he's mixing it with the
men as well
first time we've seen he held it well
after you show the judges that you're in
control of the artist and forward
somersault the other component to the
dive 1.9 the degree of difficulty really
get a tight bike in there the attempt
she was at that
they to the 7.5 that's a decent score
given the degree of difficulty and we
put him into fifth place the platform
now one three hours the diver seemed to
be from Canada comes back quiet game
simple die the reverse dive and
providing the degree of difficulty
position with the hands on the thighs
for quite a while I call you snap back
into the entry position several a half's
was a couple of eighths they were struck
off 40 2.75 into fourth place at the
moment for from Canada
now the Egyptian this reverse dive
untie the entry good to see two divers
at this booth Olympic Games from the
Egyptians limited training training the
winter in Egypt and all pulling for them
to practicing like yeah
judges at all I'm tiny five 5.5 hundred
sixes to nine point four or five
these are also the points that are taken
forward to the five of the first four
dice giving Garcia Alvarez of Colombia
taking the three meter competition
tidy on the entry simple dives you've
got to get it right the way the state
will be amplified schools are multiplied
to get our points score
I don't think about me happy enough with
seven seven and a half's one eight one
six one four they're struck through of
course
[Music]
this is about he needs to stop needing
some dives
oh dear here lopez reverse dive simple
dive
too bad getting chance for the clay
the judges will be overly impressed that
Pike position you need to get your head
right up against your legs I'm going to
do that I've had ed treatment seven the
house across the board it's enough to
put it into third place except the
Frenchman it's gender another reverse
dive for these simple dies early on the
degree of difficulty is being capped
okay
setting the world on fire without dive
disgrace himself need to have a really
tight don't give that pike the tiny
entry
not as high as you like six and a half
and sevens but it won't go five enough
to put it into joy the sixth place at
the moment to put one of the difficulty
here a reverse somersault half twist and
see Miss before in this round so a
difficult one for the Singaporean
well elegantly done but the energy
wasn't great
[Applause]
as crisp as the judges were hoping for
they're going in to this Ryan's
and over rotation not hugely liked by
the judges sixes was 15.5 in there and
he is dying in tents at the moments as
we conclude at third round and good news
everybody was crammed in here
Ivan 55.3 piano and quite a bit of
difference through here and put it tied
chenko and then very close between third
fourth fifth it's a little bit distance
so when you get down to 10th johnson
Chanin but I brought in the Egyptian
unity levels 50 60 points the difference
already after three rounds between top
and bottom
great to see so many people coming in
for the preliminary rounds enjoying what
they can see their pens are off for some
of these athletes there's a professor of
microbiology a chap to his choice
Jenko all for ukraine ready to go three
meter have more success second after
three rounds this will be a reverse dive
last round of course where the
difficulty to critically is count
that's pretty good
so the pike nice and tight
touching the knees that's what you want
to see the hands against the legs and
then bring the round tie diamond not
spectacular sevens almost across the
board from the judges 39.9 momentarily
here we go into lead
and ripple around this printed Center as
a difficult dive this one forward one
1/2 so I sort of had one twist it was
good
after getting to the water we scored
consistently well
over 50 points in the first or the
second and third dies
[Music]
do the same again here 56.7 knowings
mostly from the judges they really the
city David Barker is me
and I don't need you don't know he
ensign to put time for him as well we're
gonna vote rotation when he came in to
the water the elements in the air look
pretty good as well two point one of the
degree of difficulty gotta get into the
dive quickly get all the elements out
the way a little bit too into that died
position perhaps but so given the degree
of difficulty dead alright okay five
minutes Eve third at the moments
go Ukraine looking good earlier Timo
Bart out rockin
apart just a simple reverse dive that we
did 1.9 and first mere mortals are all
difficult from 10 meters look at this as
tight as you might like into the pipe
and a pretty straight entry into the
water
judges like it he was 198.50 m 8:40 8.45
that's decent that will push him into
third place
that's soggy sad
next up of Armenia forward sums up 1/2
is 2 point 1 the degree of difficulty
little bit early into the water quite
going in vertically
ten meter specialist let's see this
entry here not too bad six point five is
the judges forty point nine five he goes
into fifth
Finch Canadian honey Montreal penny Pitt
County hate that wasn't too bad
[Applause]
summer soap one twist
for your position I'm gonna get into
that Pike position some salt simple
twist just a little bit of mobile
rotation starting mark sevens go into
fourth place the Egyptian forward double
somersault this a two point four degree
of difficulty so he's had the simple
dice but now he's really going to go for
it had low marks before 9.45 better here
well it didn't hold it in the arms town
for long enough the judges need to see
that you've got that under control and
he will be punished for that what you
going you're going double somersault
certainly there the degree of difficulty
he's been marked ok 65.5 40 48 the time
being leads up into seventh place but
there are calls for more divers to go in
this fourth round Kevin I see it however
this this is a tricky dive back one
twist a half twist rather
but ideas enter into the water
to particular type I knew that
so at his entry not quite getting it
right not quite to lovely vertical
position like Missy but given the degree
of difficulty he's done all right
a score of 41 into six place he goes it
makes good he's a good dive here that's
not a bad one
for one a half somersault one twist it's
important what the degree of difficulty
[Music]
face that's a bit was entry wasn't too
bad at all
respectable
I like standing there your Lopez you
have been hoping for better default the
place with two Nevarez these 42 points
behind
like some so our twist on the Frenchman
makes agenda
well sir we have the luxury of looking
at the replay making our judgments the
judges of course look at it live make
the decision seven times and a 7.5 Paula
French went into 6th place he goes
just one more athlete to go in this
fourth round and ready Jonathan with
China Singapore with an arm stand for
somersault and switched to gymnastic
property monastics at the age of 12 he
should be able to harm standard nothing
else
splash upon the entry to the dive be
particularly happy with that point 9 the
degree of difficulty but he how about
lovely and they threw enormous long time
the judges liked the entry particularly
twenty eight and a half points in price
well it's going well for you now look at
the difference between him and her Genco
but look at the battle for second and
third and fourth very tight less than
five points between those athletes and
then it's the battle the rest to the
bottom between their chana dal quarries
are we having their own personal battle
down there the bottom bottom of the
rankings
into the fifth round the calf of the
degree of difficulty goes away these
scores carry forward to the final but it
is where we get the spectacular dies so
put it
Genco we look forward for a year a half
somersault they keep our back with two
and a half service old one and a half
twists the dive coming later
you can see the crowd enjoying and he
step up in difficulty real test for
these young athletes
and we're twisting into the somersaults
not about entry
handling scores from the Jenny's sixty
five point six though given the degree
of difficulty you'll see the schools
going up just for the time being now
then three point two degree of
difficulty
a chair and they cried gotta get into
those somersaults as quickly as you
possibly can to give you enough time to
slight the entry into the water looking
about entry is it as good as some of his
other scores eight from the judges
but given the degree of difficulty the
score seventy six point eight there's 48
points ahead the top moments now in 1703
meter we consisted there's no major
mistakes and we have seen many here
either for three and a half seven so
degree of difficulty is three didn't hit
the entry at all well under rotated and
they will be punished by the judges for
that so difficult you've got a
concentrate first of all getting these
somersaults out of the way and then he
just didn't have enough time so you get
the dive in that's why he's getting low
marks from the judges five hours and
fives it we disappointed with that
you know the part out of Germany the
after round for a very tight battle
Stan double somersault with what a half
twist three point two into a difficulty
again a little bit lacking in time to
get into that diet and died position to
get into the water really got to be
quick into the somersaults struggling
for time to site that die little bit
under rotated 6006 is from the judges
may give some of these rivals around
looking for second third place
opportunity that disappointed with that
was these points not being pushed
forward to the final
yeah there was three of the most
somersaults
gave top grade on the entry covered it
for a very long time on the 10-meter
platform really got to get some
ourselves out of the way as quickly as
possible because you're running out of
that six is six and a half for that we
went through some salt for left sorry
goose am sixteen point eight to fourth
place he goes
video yet of Canada another Edward
three-and-a-half somersault same as we
saw from the Albanian saki-san
if anything over-rotated on that
not quite hitting the entries here the
athletes at the moment
if it untied you with the feet as well
marked down as a result 62 the 6.5 and
it's a fourth place for the Canadian
we're back
well the Egyptian going through a
forward three and a half somersault and
the degree of difficulty of three
no rotation on entry
do me like the resources with his home
country his excellent work sixes from
the judges over-rotation
as you can see entered the water fifty
for the score to seven face for the time
being as we go the Colombian Kevin
Garcia Alvarez dies game over rotation
on that three and a half somersault very
quick getting through the somersaults
have enough time just to cite the entry
there great flexibility these athletes
have
6007 s60 the score see they're just
indicating to his coach the entry for
place to the last round
okay rotation from the next unit also a
little bit on these more complex dyes
[Applause]
really like the over rotation means it's
a disappointment for five sixes build is
a big rival but at the moment he is in
fifth place and of course the points in
the first four dives go forward to the
point this is just for these guys
didn't hit the entry at all well that
[Applause]
lasts for three hours seven salt said
the somersaults all right I'm out of
time to get in and ready for entering
the water falls
you can't have any complaints about
dining tonight he goes legacy for the
rueful smile he knew what the problem
was
dr. Jam then his own personal battle of
the moments we have elk or deep bottom
of the rankings look to have some
results with a twist
well the worst time you see a game entry
I'm standing here Singaporeans here in
the crowd you put me here and cheering
and you like what they saw is not so
impressed not so bad I'll hear three
sixes
four of the judges he still stays ahead
about four points from the Egyptian
interesting at the top though look at
the difference between first and second
but then a battle between second third
it's quite tight and between fourth and
fifth as well and there's not personal
battle between China now according at
the bottom and Shankar will be
disappointedly down there as well 96 of
5 5 points
so if it's right done and dusted we move
on to round six of nine is a good order
and we're waiting from you Queenie until
it I checked Coby get us underway to
qualify
all the athletes you qualified in that
qualifier here leave the country the
right to be there
he was second after the last round what
nailing the entry there was so quick
get these service oats out of the way
and then quickly look at where you're
going to round that it was over rotating
six-six house no word is touching the
next diver on the platform there he is
three and a half somersault 3.3 the
degree of difficulty
I heard by country mile at the moment
they cheer from the crowd
SPI of course he has school attend one
of his judges he's enjoying his games at
the moment already has gold in the three
meter and that was not bad at all was it
decent entry as well nine judges eighty
nine point eight the score he's heading
towards a hundred point advantage and
his rivals they know the answer then
they reverse two and a half some sort
for the Norwegian not the most difficult
dive you'll see these latter stages
[Applause]
nantan meddled in the European Junior
Championships
me to the world of the European
Championship level as well as various
showing through that with eight seven
and a half to third place he goes to the
bottlenecks our German athletes three
metre platform better here
people at all right under rotated a
little bit undercooked it's a right
angle between the body and the legs as
he tries to know this in Word through a
somersault
this is a bit that's going to consider
the judges
as a result he's marked a half 52.8 is
disappointing for the German sonica son
the European Junior Championships this
year 10 meter board is in fact three and
a half cents
when it was a 3.6 degree of difficulty
that's the most difficult you're going
to see in these three rounds he's got
two of them in his routine a little bit
of OB rotation
that's why the judges of octave die in
fives and five and a half swell still
getting that half decent score because
of that degree of difficulty but he'll
be disappointed three point three degree
of difficulty for the Canadian if you
leave go in the 810 assault
which is a little bit undercooked
[Applause]
rotated that such a learning curve for
these athletes to that tuck position
knees up to the chest
Oh disaster that's for sure six and a
half from the judges sixty four point
three five into third place for the
Canadian elk or T of YouTube Nextup
level three and a half seven three point
is the degree of difficulty
thank you a little bit untidy a bit of
over-rotation it's quickly seeing here
along with my Gouda new Egyptians taking
part in these Youth Olympic Games five
five and a half
the judges have decided
51.2 the score entirely into seventh
place
now the club you came in Garcia over
this
and stronger on the platform
okay in with three hours of assault
three-point to the degree of difficulty
[Music]
just a little bit over rotated entry
marks on the judges seven there's seven
and a half and he'll be happy with that
score which puts him into fourth place
this man needs to step up to like a
little bit Mexican we beam him up at the
moment
coach likes it
he's a long way away from young how even
some of the other drivers better from
him sevens of 7 in the house Jody is 70
point for would be enough to put him
into third place
now the Frenchman
don't last time I didn't enjoy that they
do this in with three and a half seven
salt
again not a great entry into the water
it struggling a little bit and his dies
just sixteen years of age seventeen
until October towards for the Youth
Olympic Games you hit that four-year
cycle you're 18 got a slight advantage I
think it's fair to say sevens over six
and a half not too bad
it's a ninth place is likely to stay sad
with a forward three and a half cents
off between difficulty
it's not too bad a bit untidy into the
water Singaporean contingent happy to
give him every support they Karen good
position right just a little bit over
rotated
sixth house too bad for John the man
from Singapore the near five at the ACS
school in Singapore still the students
only competing in the 10 meter and look
at that look at the difference between
first and second and look how close it
is between the second third while all
they don't to 6 really all could change
in the next 3 days 9 rounds of course I
have a decent battle at the bottom has
went over to the French wind the
Singaporean and the land for in Egypt so
three more dives to go
for each athlete and chance to show what
they can do listen really eye-catching
dies live check coat man in his first of
the 11 to go
to go competed in the European Junior
Championships twelfth and return me to
well this one in word three and a half
cents
what do you God
perfect entry into the water as the
boats push away from the platform yeah
not a fan entry that the judges like it
88.5 scrub through seventy six point
eight he's been there all there abouts
all the way through so that it was about
yang out here he is the home favorite
three point four degree of difficulty
this reverse half somersault
difficult dives coming up next one will
be 3.5 mm it's a nice now these
to back her hair
it's an awful long way down there's a
lot of things that could go wrong and he
is looking in a class of his own at the
moment getting nice and tight in that
tuck position early to the diver what a
beautiful entry as well and nines on the
judges 19.5 one charge of the main point
from a couple of 8.5 91 point eight
he's edging their Eve Airy closely to a
advantage of over a hundred points very
handsome now
somersaults him
get into the water at all well we're
still looking to extend the legs and
didn't manage it he knows it look about
good dismay too pretty on replay that
will knock him down on that vacuum way
down as well we've got the ability
wrongs in the European Junior
Championships this year and three of
them are very consistent in the three
meter no major mistakes but that's one
there will be hoping to get that out of
the system before the finals later on of
course
these more complex dive don't count
towards don't carry for the first four
dives are so a disaster
during the entry not perfect moving that
back three and a half seven salt tricky
dive three point three the degree of
difficulty stronger on the springboard
disaster those sevens scores he'll take
through sixty nine point three into
third place he goes for second third and
fourth
and some of you signed off on being yet
they reversed three and a half cents out
three point four degree of difficulty to
get this right
he will school well
well not quite nailing the entry the
same i fairly tidied I'd want to make
sure you've got that clearance of calls
from the platform good push out get the
somersaults out of the way make sure
you've got time to site your entry I
think was probably the problem
sevens almost across the forward got
from one six point five into fourth
place for the Albanian he was fourth in
this position coming into this round
stands
so whatever off to us it's a tricky one
this
well a bit of difficulty holding the arm
stand you need to make sure that some of
the control you'll be marked down
otherwise by the judges
looking to get the achromatic element
out of the way as soon as possible
so you like that to entry into the water
a little bit untidy into the water and
six hours and 6s for Gagne you're
staying fourth place
I have L told you one of the athletes it
it comes the spirit of the Youth Olympic
Games it's not gonna meddle but he is
going to give it everything is a two and
a half or two half summer so with two
twists
the energy wasn't the greatest but it
was a degree of difficulty of 3:23
hurried through the elements and
also not particularly ready for knives
well you know it's all experienced this
guy 17 years of age here is a 15 year
old 16 until next month it's going to
see
going in and we rotated and I'm at back
three and a half somersault difficult
died with the arms round quicker than
that
a disaster 7s from the judges couldn't
have to put him into third place keeping
in third place
now the next finish been a bit off form
I think it's fair to say today the arms
times a somersault
what the ha
me too qualifying events it's fair to
say it looks more comfortable at 3 meter
the silver in the 3-meter so we thought
there's going to be running and looking
for a medal here but not so sure it's
going to happen
get to the finals tonight's six is he
was telling his coach undercook that
dive like this
Shanda
going into this round 759 of course back
two and a half so it's not not the most
difficult we've seen in this round
oh don't need me to tell you hit that
horribly into the water markdown and
then some like the judges to that type
of addiction well nearly didn't complete
dive
just as I got away with it but the
judges are going hot so be going easy on
him three in the house yeah get the move
on now then here Jonathan chant
youngster former gymnast and then inward
three and somersaults
a little bit early on the entry you know
a few ragged dies in a way it doesn't
matter because this is all about the
ranking for the final it's a good time
to get these ragged edges shaved off
gained very very entry by quite some
distance fours and a half as we said the
first four dies easier dies points going
forward
look at the difference here almost 100
points of the Yang and the chenko but
much tighter look at that between third
fourth fifth sick
to see who the rankings are for the
final no doctor who's going to be ranked
number one
some of the athletes just knocking off
the noise with some headphones as we
head towards for nod to it round round
eight of nine here is a check coat
you have to do better over three metres
they're all there abouts do better here
right second going into this eighth
round
you know dive here
but it was a good hold but again the
entry wasn't perfect three point to the
degree of difficulty understand that
double somersault with one and a half
twists
essentially just a little bit
over-rotated 6's from the judges 57:26
has been consistently the best of the
rest to this man you know how this is
his biggest dive
3.5 the degree of difficulty announced
I'm back triple somersault take his time
over this
she was a great
very difficulty
put some pressure on this young man 16
year old look at that perfect position
but over-rotated the crowd didn't like
what they saw for the judges now short
yang won't either Falls the coach
straight in to have a word chip away at
the advantage all right relatively
simply back to half service sauce
it undercooked on the entry
I looked under rotated every punished
for that and they got the bronze in the
European Junior Championships in the
10-meter but that's not the best time
they'll ever do a little bit early into
the water pours getting serious here
next up Germany's female fart out of all
European junior champion last month this
completely different fish of course
that's true then have some salt oh dear
didn't hit that one at all slap to the
back of the legs as he entered the water
and once again we see a rounded low
scores here it's a long session we told
you that's ugly
everywhere you look at it long session
all these divers be tiring
that's excellent experience for them
it's not excellent scores for TV Bartel
mark you down at three Wow will it be
better for live psychics on seventh
going into this round yeah I understand
back double somersault what I don't have
twists three point to the degree of
difficulty
when she wasn't too bad
fell off the platform a lot of attack in
the dive was the push to get the
momentum too bad
better than last couple of days six of a
house is it 42.4 enough to put him into
third place
hotels disappointing dive the Canadian
reverse somersault this is a difficult
dive three point four degree of
difficulty an over rotation this time
really difficult in this eighth round
these concentrations practicing
experience of course we forget divers of
course a half five and it's enough to
push you up into fourth place so I said
is it third after a better than the rest
dive
in a Gyptian we'll have outdoor
with a rotation but given his
inexperience he'll be happy without 3.3
the degree of difficulty hasn't been
scoring heavily in the latter rounds the
effort certainly gives it a go not
scared
only threes for the judges almost across
the board one for just fuck off at all
the shorter attention span the sort of
focus you need in the final will help
only five rounds of course nine rounds
here this one a bit more of a marathon
than a sprint
see how nice next up Colombian
there we go long as you control that
it's done all right there's no great
shakes but he got away with it well if
you have to come back down and reset
again to died you automatically lose two
points so you didn't want to do that
fair play to him that ability the
gymnastic department than most of us
could muster a little bit of a rotation
in the entry into the water but well
consuming what we've seen in this rain
before you know be happened with 5.5
didn't hit the entry at all well we've
seen that a little bit this eighth round
the legs getting a slap of water did
snap the legs over given the degree of
difficulty five point five and six he's
top down in the last couple of rounds
I have to put him up into third place at
the moment given the free-for-all we've
had in this round in sixes and 30s sham
diet for spoiling rains proving slowly
that was okay
[Applause]
move back two and a half somersaults in
half twists Pike position didn't really
in a tight bike position the judges were
satisfied enough seven six and a half 64
into 8 place Jan points the Egyptian
Corey possibly to Daniel in some
difficulty to a half sentence
so tiny half dive not the greatest entry
into the water
big chairs so near that diving platform
the Singaporean contingent like giving
every encouragement represented
Singapore the age youth games entirely
going into the water you'll be punished
as well five five and a half touching
distance of dancing what is the
preliminary of course to your type the
rankings going into the final everyone
make it to the final not losing anybody
disappointing eighth dive very close in
the midfield in third fourth fifth sixth
as well come and raise something to the
Youth Olympic Games we have certainly
enjoyed their enthusiastic support and a
really good turnout here again in this
auditorium just part of the Olympic
sport centre fabulous
and pointed Center
so from the 802 getting into the sixty
points a lot of mistakes being made what
are my difficulty difficulty dives of
course as Ron if you can nail them then
it's amplified in the score of course as
we said the middle three scores count
then they're added together and
multiplied by the different difficulty
so if you can get a half-decent score
with a difficult dive you're doing okay
this man is doing okay second at the
moment as we go into our last dives and
my friend
so chain code three point three they did
really difficulty here a chance to do
well
let's go to that entry a little bit
wanting three half cent results
tucked position the tightest up your
leather seat little bit twisted as he
wedding on that entry yes has been
punished by the judges the sharpest of
sharp eyes that need a replay to pick
out the faults
so yang showed he was bobble in the last
round just 42 points we do here
and the carminative vowel 3.2 the degree
of difficulty filled on two more summers
off with one and a half twists
[Applause]
nice entry as well
let's get the schools as well coming
through for the judges nine and a half
and nines back on form for young now
just a reminder if anyone thought
a little bit of fun ability about him
after the eighth round that doesn't
matter I can still pull it back so then
Daniel gets in with his last dive three
point two they did real difficulty back
to announce themselves with whatever
half twists
a great entry
[Applause]
this is an 18 year old cease our time in
Norway
it is from Oslo waiting from home at the
moment
62 on for from Google wait man the
German team Hobart out standing seventh
rotated going in on that factor a half
somersault with one a half twists to
your difficulty
i century though six is six of a half's
from the judges 59.2 to third place
momentarily of course for a forum around
the large field you might see at the
Olympics
just 11 it's gonna be 12
they're soggy side of Armenia
60 degree of difficulty here do well
here he will school very heavily I
always take this time to put a platform
that's not at all bad given the
complexity of that fact to a half
somersaults two and a half twists in the
pike position
nicely done
so then the Canadian Philip Gagne
so you point to the degree of difficulty
[Applause]
so look at this dive
a bit of over-rotation that
but forgiving 6 is that was one 7 there
so then the Egyptian law have alcohol D
his last type of this competition a
three point four so a difficult time
I've reversed three and a half
somersault
two fuel dies in this last round
you know what not the greatest I've but
he's done so well he's competed hard
here got the somersaults in not a great
entry into the water
and opposition well about entry fine
certainly you know judges they'll be
struck off forty four point two he's a
school that have you please of no fee
something's showing promise the Egyptian
can it Garcia Alvarez ambien forth going
into his last round
something he always does a little bit
I'm tired entry into the water to half
somersaults one and a half twist a
little bit over-rotated not bad marks
from the judges quite like what they see
three point to the degree of difficulty
so the sevens with it at a decent score
now then a three point six degree of
difficulty those in this round thanks
good Rodrigo de Lopez after myself
two and a half twist
just about got away with it to hurry on
that entry in being completely under
rotated on entry it's not a bad dive
difficult difficult dive to do judges
invite to brown about seven that's a
decent score of 75 point six up into
third place that's better from the
Mexican eats languished in the mid
rankings for quite some time
alexis jean de our next up two more
dives in this Plumeri
around on the 10-meter platform this is
three point two degree difficulty double
somersault one and a half twists
she's not great in under-cooks
we have to hold it in that time for
quite some time when you go go hard go
quickly
what about sevens across the board apart
for about one six point five sixty seven
point two for electives and odd
next up Jonathan Chan the youngster the
student from Singapore three point three
the difficulty for this back three and a
half Sanderson
little bit under-rotated difficult dive
forward qian we've got some really good
and interesting dives and a much better
quality of diving in this ninth round
compared to the eights rain
a little bit under rotated and as a
result forward 1/2 simplifies for a chug
just enough to take him ahead of will
have alcohol D of course all these
couples qualified we're just sorting out
the rankings here these are the rankings
look over a hundred points the
difference between young and live saga
so real quality for young at the top end
saigo-san and i could come back from
Diego Lopez as well tighten the team
that all those Garcia Alvarez not far
away either
Jenko dropped away towards the end China
I think it's fair to say on course for
that double-double of gold medals
and that's the pillar he's out of the
way and final comes later the fans here
enjoyed these nine rounds of diving and
yeah how it's giving the local support
something to cheer about some absolutely
fabulous dive some tens in there as well
will be pleased with how it's gone for
China this morning in the preliminary
competition
[Music]
it's a great action here then in the
preliminaries what is clear is it yeah
how the Chinese diver is the man to try
and catch as we head towards the finals
of this 10 metre platform competition